Samantha Dickeson

Full-stack web developer

Current student at Founders and Coders, learning full-stack web development. I'm a Psychology graduate with a 2:1 honours degree from the University of Reading, and previously worked in data analysis for four years. I am proficient in MS Excel and Access, with some self-taught VBA and SQL. I know a smattering of Python.

- → github.com/starsuit
- → starsuit.github.io
- → linkedin.com/in/samantha-dickeson
- → samlucydickeson@gmail.com

FOUNDERS AND CODERS

Founders and Coders, Finsbury Park

MARCH 2019 - JULY 2019

Founders and Coders are a non-profit based in Finsbury Park, London. They run peer-led full-stack web development courses which are free but highly selective.

There is a heavy focus on cooperation and all our coding is done by pair programming.

I'm looking forward to learning React in the coming weeks, as well as gaining some experience working on some exciting tech for better projects with my fellow students.

EXPERIENCE

Vanguard Learning Trust, Ickenham — *Data Manager*

DECEMBER 2015 - MARCH 2019

My responsibilities included analysing student performance data for target setting and reporting to senior leadership. I gained a lot of experience in MS Excel and Google Sheets, using VBA and Google Apps Script to create dynamic reports and data visualisations.

Xerox UK, Uxbridge — Data Migration Analyst

MARCH 2015 - DECEMBER 2015

I managed qualification related data on the company data system SAP. As I picked up VBA and SQL, I began to produce mini 'applications' for employees and managers to access and transfer data.

STACK / SKILLS

- ❖ HTML and CSS
- Accessibility and design
- ❖ Git and GitHub
- Vanilla JavaScript
- Test-driven development
- Node and npm
- HTTP server
- Express
- Handlebars
- ❖ PostgreSQL
- Heroku deployment

EDUCATION

Reading University — BSc Psychology 2:1

OCTOBER 2010 - JUNE 2014

Vyners School, Ickenham SEPTEMBER 2003 - JULY 2010